<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quiz App Using Java</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="this_is_a_arrow_icon">This is a arrow icon</string>


    <!--category name here-->
    <string-array name="category_names">
        <item>General Knowledge Category</item>
        <item>Science Category</item>
        <item>Technology Category</item>
        <item>Entertainment Category</item>
        <item>Sports Category</item>
        <item>Literature Category</item>
        <item>Arts and Culture Category</item>
        <item>Food and Drink Category</item>
        <item>Mathematics Category</item>
        <item>Language and Words Category</item>
        <item>Nature and Environment Category</item>
        <item>Mythology Category</item>
    </string-array>
    <!--category description name here-->
    <string-array name="category_descriptions">
        <item>General Knowledge Category</item>
        <item>Science Category</item>
        <item>Technology Category</item>
        <item>Entertainment Category</item>
        <item>Sports Category</item>
        <item>Literature Category</item>
        <item>Arts and Culture Category</item>
        <item>Food and Drink Category</item>
        <item>Mathematics Category</item>
        <item>Language and Words Category</item>
        <item>Nature and Environment Category</item>
        <item>Mythology Category</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- General Knowledge Sub Categories -->
    <string-array name="general_knowledge_sub_categories">
        <item>World Geography</item>
        <item>History and Civilization</item>
        <item>Science and Technology</item>
        <item>Current Affairs</item>
        <item>General Science</item>
        <item>Famous Personalities</item>
        <!-- Add more subcategories for General Knowledge as needed -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="general_knowledge_sub_categories_description">
        <item>Explore the world\'s continents, countries, and landmarks.</item>
        <item>Learn about historical events, cultures, and civilizations.</item>
        <item>Discover advancements in science and the latest technologies.</item>
        <item>Stay informed about current events and news from around the globe.</item>
        <item>Understand fundamental principles of physics, chemistry, and biology.</item>
        <item>Get to know influential figures who have made a significant impact.</item>
        <!-- Add more descriptions for General Knowledge subcategories as needed -->
    </string-array>

    <!-- Science Category -->
    <string-array name="science_questions">
        <item>What is the chemical symbol for water?</item>
        <item>Who is considered the father of modern physics?</item>
        <item>How does photosynthesis occur in plants?</item>
        <item>What is the largest planet in our solar system?</item>
        <item>What is the speed of light in a vacuum?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="science_descriptions">
        <item>Explore the world of chemistry and biology with questions about elements and compounds.</item>
        <item>Learn about groundbreaking scientists and their contributions to the field of physics.</item>
        <item>Understand the process by which plants convert sunlight into energy.</item>
        <item>Discover facts about the planets in our solar system, including their sizes and characteristics.</item>
        <item>Delve into the fundamentals of physics with questions about the speed of light and related concepts.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Technology Category -->
    <string-array name="technology_questions">
        <item>Who co-founded Microsoft along with Bill Gates?</item>
        <item>What is the significance of Moore\'s Law in computing?</item>
        <item>Which programming language is often used for mobile app development?</item>
        <item>What does the acronym "URL" stand for?</item>
        <item>Which company is known for producing the iPhone and iPad?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="technology_descriptions">
        <item>Explore the history of technology and its pioneers with questions about notable figures.</item>
        <item>Understand the impact of Moore\'s Law on the development of computer technology.</item>
        <item>Learn about programming languages commonly used in creating applications for mobile devices.</item>
        <item>Discover the meaning behind common technology-related acronyms, such as "URL."</item>
        <item>Get insights into companies that have played a significant role in the tech industry.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Entertainment Category -->
    <string-array name="entertainment_questions">
        <item>Who won the Academy Award for Best Actor in 2021?</item>
        <item>Which film is often considered the highest-grossing of all time?</item>
        <item>Who is known as the "Queen of Pop" in the music industry?</item>
        <item>What is the name of the fictional wizarding school in the Harry Potter series?</item>
        <item>Which TV series features the phrase "Winter is coming"?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="entertainment_descriptions">
        <item>Stay updated on the world of entertainment with questions about recent award winners.</item>
        <item>Explore the realm of cinema with questions about box office records and popular films.</item>
        <item>Learn about iconic figures in the music industry and their nicknames.</item>
        <item>Immerse yourself in the magical world of literature with questions about famous wizarding schools.</item>
        <item>Test your knowledge of popular TV series with questions about famous catchphrases.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Sports Category -->
    <string-array name="sports_questions">
        <item>Who holds the record for the most Olympic gold medals in swimming?</item>
        <item>Which country hosted the FIFA World Cup in 2018?</item>
        <item>Who is often referred to as "The Greatest" in the history of boxing?</item>
        <item>What is the highest score ever achieved in a single NBA game?</item>
        <item>Which tennis player has won the most Grand Slam singles titles?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sports_descriptions">
        <item>Explore the world of swimming and the achievements of record-breaking Olympic athletes.</item>
        <item>Test your knowledge of FIFA World Cup history with questions about host countries.</item>
        <item>Learn about legendary boxers and their impact on the sport of boxing.</item>
        <item>Discover remarkable performances in NBA history with questions about high scores.</item>
        <item>Get insights into the achievements of tennis players who have excelled in Grand Slam events.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Literature Category -->
    <string-array name="literature_questions">
        <item>Who wrote the play "Romeo and Juliet"?</item>
        <item>What is the main theme of the novel "1984" by George Orwell?</item>
        <item>Which author is known for the "Harry Potter" book series?</item>
        <item>What is the title of Jane Austen\'s most famous novel?</item>
        <item>Who wrote the poem "The Raven"?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="literature_descriptions">
        <item>Explore the world of classic literature with questions about famous playwrights.</item>
        <item>Discuss the themes and dystopian elements of George Orwell\'s novel "1984."</item>
        <item>Test your knowledge of modern literature with questions about popular book series.</item>
        <item>Learn about the works of Jane Austen, a prominent figure in English literature.</item>
        <item>Discover the poet behind the hauntingly beautiful poem "The Raven."</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Arts and Culture Category -->
    <string-array name="arts_and_culture_questions">
        <item>Who painted the Mona Lisa?</item>
        <item>What art movement is characterized by bright colors and bold shapes?</item>
        <item>Which famous architect designed the Sydney Opera House?</item>
        <item>What is the name of the traditional Japanese tea ceremony?</item>
        <item>Who is known as the "father of modern dance"?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="arts_and_culture_descriptions">
        <item>Explore the world of visual arts with questions about iconic paintings and painters.</item>
        <item>Learn about art movements that have left a lasting impact on the art world.</item>
        <item>Discover the architects behind some of the world\'s most famous landmarks.</item>
        <item>Immerse yourself in the traditions of Japanese culture with questions about tea ceremonies.</item>
        <item>Understand the contributions of influential figures in the field of modern dance.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Food and Drink Category -->
    <string-array name="food_and_drink_questions">
        <item>What is the main ingredient in guacamole?</item>
        <item>Which country is known for inventing sushi?</item>
        <item>What is the primary ingredient in the Italian dish risotto?</item>
        <item>Which type of wine is often paired with seafood?</item>
        <item>What is the national dish of India?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_and_drink_descriptions">
        <item>Test your knowledge of popular dishes with questions about their main ingredients.</item>
        <item>Explore the origins of international cuisine with questions about cultural food inventions.</item>
        <item>Learn about the ingredients that make Italian risotto a delicious and comforting dish.</item>
        <item>Discover the art of wine pairing with questions about matching wines with specific foods.</item>
        <item>Explore the rich and diverse flavors of Indian cuisine with questions about its national dish.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Mathematics Category -->
    <string-array name="mathematics_questions">
        <item>What is the value of pi (π) to two decimal places?</item>
        <item>Which branch of mathematics deals with the properties of shapes and figures?</item>
        <item>What is the sum of the angles in a triangle?</item>
        <item>Who is known for the development of calculus?</item>
        <item>What is the Pythagorean theorem?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mathematics_descriptions">
        <item>Test your knowledge of mathematical constants with questions about the value of pi.</item>
        <item>Explore different branches of mathematics with questions about geometry and shapes.</item>
        <item>Understand the fundamental principles of geometry with questions about triangle angles.</item>
        <item>Learn about influential mathematicians who made significant contributions to calculus.</item>
        <item>Discover the famous theorem that relates the sides of a right triangle.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Language and Words Category -->
    <string-array name="language_and_words_questions">
        <item>What is the longest word in the English language?</item>
        <item>Which language has the most native speakers in the world?</item>
        <item>What is an anagram of the word "listen"?</item>
        <item>Who is the author of the play "Romeo and Juliet"?</item>
        <item>What is the term for a word that is spelled the same backward as forward?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="language_and_words_descriptions">
        <item>Test your knowledge of the English language with questions about long words.</item>
        <item>Explore linguistic diversity with questions about languages with the most native speakers.</item>
        <item>Challenge your word skills with questions about anagrams and wordplay.</item>
        <item>Test your knowledge of classic literature with questions about famous playwrights.</item>
        <item>Learn about words that form the same word when spelled backward.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Nature and Environment Category -->
    <string-array name="nature_and_environment_questions">
        <item>What is the largest mammal on Earth?</item>
        <item>Which gas makes up the majority of Earth\'s atmosphere?</item>
        <item>What is the process by which plants make their own food using sunlight?</item>
        <item>What is the term for the loss of a species from a particular habitat?</item>
        <item>Which planet is known as the "Red Planet"?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="nature_and_environment_descriptions">
        <item>Explore the wonders of the natural world with questions about Earth\'s largest mammals.</item>
        <item>Learn about the composition of Earth\'s atmosphere with questions about major gases.</item>
        <item>Understand the process of photosynthesis with questions about how plants produce their own food.</item>
        <item>Explore ecological concepts with questions about the loss of species from specific habitats.</item>
        <item>Discover interesting facts about the fourth planet from the Sun, known as the "Red Planet."</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Mythology Category -->
    <string-array name="mythology_questions">
        <item>Who is the king of the gods in Greek mythology?</item>
        <item>What is the name of the Norse god of thunder?</item>
        <item>Which mythical creature is part lion and part eagle?</item>
        <item>Who is the goddess of wisdom in ancient Greek mythology?</item>
        <item>What is the Hindu god of creation and destruction?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mythology_descriptions">
        <item>Explore ancient Greek mythology with questions about the king of the gods.</item>
        <item>Learn about Norse mythology with questions about the god associated with thunder.</item>
        <item>Discover mythical creatures with questions about creatures that combine different animals.</item>
        <item>Explore the pantheon of ancient Greek gods with questions about the goddess of wisdom.</item>
        <item>Learn about Hindu mythology with questions about the god responsible for creation and destruction.</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>